Guide to the Ezra Stiles College, Yale University, Student Records for the Classes of 1963-2001 Maintained by the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Ezra Stiles College, Yale University, student records for the Classes of 1963-2001 maintained by the dean
1959-2001
RU 161
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
114.25
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Ezra Stiles College, Yale University.
Ezra Stiles College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-M-1 (YRG 13-M-1), Records of the dean of Ezra Stiles College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by the dean of Ezra Stiles College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Ezra Stiles College (Yale University); Yale University -- Students
- Student records for the Class of 1963, Accession 19ND-A-325
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2039
- Student records for the Class of 1964, Accession 19ND-A-326
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
- Student records for the Class of 1965, Accession 19ND-A-327
  Restricted until January 1, 2049
- Student records for the Class of 1966, Accession 1971-A-013
  Restricted until January 1, 2046
- Student records for the Class of 1967, Accession 19ND-A-328
  Restricted until January 1, 2050
- Student records for the Class of 1968, Accession 19ND-A-329
  Restricted until January 1, 2051
- Student records for the Class of 1969, Accession 19ND-A-330
  Restricted until January 1, 2048
- Student records for the Class of 1970, Accession 19ND-A-331
  Restricted until January 1, 2053
- Student records for the Class of 1971, Accession 19ND-A-332
- Student records for the Class of 1972, Accession 19ND-A-333
  Restricted until January 1, 2055
- Student records for the Class of 1973, Accession 1978-A-023
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2049 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Class of 1974, Accession 1979-A-045
  Records are restricted until Jan 1, 2050 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
- Student records for the Classes of 1975-1978, Accession 1975-A-019
  Records are restricted until January 1, 2055 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  Scope and Contents
  Records include Freshman Counselor reports and letters of recommendation.
  - Class of 1975
  - Class of 1976
  - Class of 1977
  - Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1975, Accession 1980-A-025
  Records contain transcripts, registration and financial aid forms and correspondence.
- Student records for the Class of 1976, Accession 1982-A-038
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Ex Students
  - Recommendations
- Student records for the Class of 1977, Accession 1982-A-039
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  - Ex-Students
  - Recommendations (Box 6–7)
- Student records for the Class of 1978, Accession 1983-A-067
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - X Class of 1978
- Student records for the Class of 1979, 1975-1979; Accession 1985-A-023
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055
  Arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Non-graduates
- Student records for the Class of 1980, Accession 1985-A-024
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  - X Class of 1980
- Student records for the Class of 1981, Accession 1987-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
  - Ex Students
- Student records for the Class of 1982, Accession 1988-A-023
  - Ex Students
- Student records for the Class of 1983, Accession 1988-A-109
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Ex Students
- Student records for the Class of 1984, Accession 1990-A-013
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  - X Class of
- Student records for the Class of 1985, Accession 1991-A-029
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1986, Accession 1992-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
  - X Class of 1986
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1992-A-067
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
  - X Class of 1987
- Student records for the Class of 1988, Accession 1994-A-021
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Withdrawn
- Student records for the Class of 1989, Accession 1994-A-137
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - X Class of 1989
- Student records for the Class of 1990, Accession 1995-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - X Class of 1990
- Student records for the Class of 1991, Accession 1997-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - X Class of 1991
- Student records for the Class of 1992, Accession 1998-A-009
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - X Class of 1992
- Student records for the Classes of 1993-1994, Accession 1999-A-048
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - Class of 1993
  - X - Class of 1993
  - Class of 1994
  - X - Class of 1994
- Student records for the Class of 1995, Accession 2002-A-051
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1996, Accession 2002-A-052
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1997, Accession 2003-A-025
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1998, Accession 2004-A-035
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 1999, Accession 2005-A-058
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2000, Accession 2007-A-035
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Withdrawals
- Student records for the Class of 2001, Accession 2008-A-034
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - Withdrawals